const quiz2data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "This time last week I ___ on a beach in Greece.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was lying", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "lied", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past continuous to show that the action was already in progress at a certain time in the past.'
   },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "I ___ a pizza last night.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was ordering", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "ordered", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple to talk about past events or states which have finished.'
   },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "My mom ___ when I got home.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was cooking", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "is cooking", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past continuous to talk about something that happened before and after a specific time.'
   },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "At 8am today, Helen ___ to work.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was driving", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "drove", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past continuous to show that the action was already in progress at a certain time in the past.'
   },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "I ___ in London for 7 years.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was living", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "lived", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple to talk about something that was true for some time in the past.'
   },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "My girlfriend and I ___ a movie at 8pm yesterday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "were watching", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "watched", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past continuous to talk about something that happened before and after a specific time.'
   },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "When I was a boy, I ___ a mile to school every day.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "walked", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "was walking", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple to talk about something that happened several times in the past.'
   },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "I ___ in a restaurant during the summer 2018.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was working", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "work", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple to talk about a permanent or long-term  situation that existed in the past. However, if the situation was temporary, we can also use the past continuous.'
   },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Albert Einstein ___ in 1955.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "died", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "has died", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple to talk about something that happened once in the past.'
   },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "During the time I started to get chest pains, I ___ tennis a lot",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was playing", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "played", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past continuous when the repeated actions or events provide a longer background to something else that happened.'
   },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "We ____ Spain three times last year.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "visited ", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "were visiting", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple rather than the past continuous when we are talking about repeated actions or events in the past.'
   },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "__ she __ tennis when she was younger?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Did / play", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Was / playing", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the past simple to talk about something that happened several times in the past.',
      help1: 'We use "did" to make questions with the past simple.'
   },
  ]
export default quiz2data
